<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SDK Sandbox</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_percent_in_list">PercentInList</string>
    <string name="jake_quote">Dude, suckin\' at something is the first step towards being sorta good at something.</string>
    <string name="jake">Jake</string>
    <string name="finn">Finn</string>
    <string name="finn_quote">I floop the Pig!</string>
    <string name="lsp_quote">My beans!</string>
    <string name="lsp">LSP</string>
    <string name="pb_quote">sometimes you want someone and you want to kiss them and be with them, but you can\'t because responsibility demands sacrifice.</string>
    <string name="pb">Princess Bubblegum</string>
    <string name="lemongrab_quote">Unacceptable!</string>
    <string name="lemongrab">Earl of Lemongrab</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact based on your message
        history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="bacon_ipsum">Bacon ipsum dolor amet ham pork belly pork, porchetta pork loin frankfurter spare ribs kielbasa. Pork loin picanha shankle, pig landjaeger leberkas tongue meatloaf. Boudin tongue jowl, tenderloin short ribs landjaeger corned beef swine chuck turducken drumstick pork loin short loin salami. Pork belly brisket pastrami, ball tip short ribs frankfurter beef hamburger. Porchetta shank beef ribs pork belly pork loin capicola tri-tip pig. Ball tip venison turkey brisket. Cow sirloin swine, landjaeger frankfurter sausage beef ribs shankle tenderloin.  Jowl ball tip capicola bacon. Venison pastrami tenderloin kielbasa swine meatball pancetta short loin bresaola sirloin salami doner pork belly. Alcatra capicola prosciutto hamburger porchetta short loin ham pork belly t-bone short ribs filet mignon corned beef pastrami. Ham hock bacon chuck brisket jerky flank ball tip tongue short ribs rump frankfurter picanha kevin. Capicola picanha brisket pork porchetta shoulder doner fatback chicken beef ribs. Hamburger short ribs shankle jerky filet mignon frankfurter turducken ball tip sausage.  Meatloaf pig turducken, short ribs bacon pork belly alcatra doner pork loin beef ribs shankle bresaola cow kielbasa. Filet mignon turducken flank ham tail jowl tenderloin meatball ribeye pork. Hamburger meatball swine beef ribs chicken ribeye pork sausage salami bresaola. T-bone bacon pork chop picanha, chicken tenderloin short ribs strip steak cow meatball hamburger salami porchetta turducken corned beef. Boudin pork chop flank frankfurter, bresaola andouille pastrami tenderloin rump short loin kielbasa meatball corned beef chicken. Kielbasa frankfurter ham hock picanha salami corned beef, rump turducken pancetta prosciutto beef ribs doner.  Jowl porchetta tongue short ribs sausage alcatra doner. Boudin meatball tenderloin short loin ham hock cupim drumstick, tail leberkas. Rump drumstick pork, pancetta turducken biltong kevin ball tip jowl. Brisket spare ribs biltong, jerky frankfurter drumstick turkey. Short loin kielbasa chuck, porchetta swine turkey boudin cow ribeye. Venison biltong prosciutto fatback.  Bresaola ball tip kielbasa porchetta beef ribs cupim pork shank corned beef alcatra. Shankle meatball kevin, cupim turkey venison spare ribs. Turducken short loin pig, tail bacon landjaeger leberkas shankle swine pork chop picanha tri-tip drumstick biltong ribeye. Shank strip steak prosciutto cupim shoulder short loin flank capicola spare ribs. Pig andouille short ribs, chicken turkey pastrami fatback tri-tip beef ribs ham hamburger capicola pork loin cupim.</string>
</resources>
